Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series B-MT, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series I. Dead Photo File, 2000s
  - 9/4/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 6)
    Also CD-ROM press kit for the film Jeepers Creepers 2, 4 color slides, and one computer-printed image.
  - 8/28/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 7)
    Also menu from a 50th Anniversary celebration for Joyce and David Dinkins, 2 press releases (1 leaf each), ms. note signed by "AR" to Elinor [Tatum], 3 color slides and 5 computer-printed images. Two prints are stuck together with tape.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan
  - 8/21/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 8)
    Also 2 computer-printed images.
    Photographer if identified: Louis Boone, Bill Moore, Gideon Manasseh
  - 8/14/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 9)
    Also handbill from American Eagle Outfitters and one image removed from an unidentified catalog.
  - 8/7/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 10)
    Also 8 computer-printed images.
    Photographer if identified: Arnold Turner, Bill Moore, Gideon Manasseh
  - 7/31/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 11)
    Also magazine Regine (Winter/Spring 2003), CD-ROM press kit for the film Tomb Raider: The Cradle of Life, dust jacket from the book Brown Skin by Susan C. Taylor, 3 leaves from Pantone Fashion Color Report Fall 2003, and one computer-printed image.
  - 7/30/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 12)
    Also press kit for The Washington Cooperatives and 2 strips of negatives (8 images).
    Photographer if identified: Ali Rahman, Bill Moore, Louis Boone, Allen Morgan, Damaso Reyes, James Levine
  - 7/17/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 13)
    Also one color slide.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Naomi White
  - 7/16/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 14)
    Also one computer-printed image and one offset-printed image.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Images of Us
  - 7/9/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 15)
    One print is a Polaroid. Also flier for furniture store Sugarhill.
    Photographer if identified: Walter Karling, Bill Moore
  - 6/26/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 16)
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Gideon Manasseh, Allen Morgan
  - 6/12/2003 (Box I-4, Folder 17)
  - Adler, Christine, & Francesca Jules (Box I-4, Folder 18)
  - Alvin Ailey Repertory Ensemble (Box I-4, Folder 19)
  - Alberta, René (Box I-4, Folder 20)
  - Alexis, Alvin, & Tony Jackson (Box I-4, Folder 21)
  - Amos, John (Box I-4, Folder 22)
  - Angelou, Maya (Box I-4, Folder 23)
  - Aska-Braggs, Monica (Box I-4, Folder 24)
  - Bailey, Shona (Box I-4, Folder 25)
  - Bartee, Rich (Box I-4, Folder 26)
    3 leaves removed from an unidentified publication.
  - Bass, Leon (Dr.) (At Buchenwald on 4/11/45) (Box I-4, Folder 27)
    Photographer if identified: Miles Educational Film ProdsInc.
  - Bass, Saul (Box I-4, Folder 28)
  - Belafonte, Harry (Box I-4, Folder 29)
  - Blackmon-Bailey, Diane (Box I-4, Folder 30)
    One offset-printed image.
  - Brandon, John (Rev.) (Box I-4, Folder 31)
  - Brath, Elombe (Box I-4, Folder 32)
  - Broadnax, Walter (Box I-4, Folder 33)
  - Brooklyn's Tree Golden (Box I-4, Folder 34)
    Photographer if identified: Kathryn Kirk
  - Brooker, George M. (Box I-4, Folder 35)
  - Brooks, James, & Jeffrey Nichols (Box I-4, Folder 36)
  - Butts, Calvin (Rev.), Paul Stephens (Rev.), Van Jay, Del Shields (Rev.), Luther Gatling, & Stephanie Mills (Box I-4, Folder 37)
    Both prints mounted on a single leaf of paper.
  - Carter, Betty (Box I-4, Folder 38)
  - Clinkscales, Keith T., Lydia Cole (Juvenile Diabetes Foundation International) (Box I-4, Folder 39)
    Photographer if identified: TAR
  - Coles, Kim (Box I-4, Folder 40)
  - Cooper (Mr.), Jeff Fox, Mark Curry, & Keri Webb (Box I-4, Folder 41)
  - Cose, Ellis, & Ron Brown (Box I-4, Folder 42)
    Photographer if identified: Oggi's Kitchen
  - Dandridge, Glenn (Box I-4, Folder 43)
  - Delany, Samuel R. (Box I-4, Folder 44)
    Photographer if identified: Becket Logan
  - Dinkins, David (Mayor) (Box I-4, Folder 45)
    One print has 2 staples through border.
  - Facemob (Box I-4, Folder 46)
    Photographer if identified: Mario Castellanos
  - Feelin' Groovy (Box I-4, Folder 47)
  - Folks, Horton (Dr.) (Box I-4, Folder 48)
  - Ford & Morgan (Box I-4, Folder 49)
  - Ford, Harold E. (Congressman) (Box I-4, Folder 50)
  - Fountain, Clarence (Box I-4, Folder 51)
    Photographer if identified: Jack Vartoogian
  - Fountain, Clarence, and the Blind Boys of Alabama (Box I-4, Folder 52)
  - Foxy Femmes (Box I-4, Folder 53)
    Promotional print for the Fox television show Living Single, originally titled My Girls.
  - Franklin, Wendy (Box I-4, Folder 54)
  - Gall, Patra & Aaron (Box I-4, Folder 55)
    Photographer if identified: Lisa Leone
  - Garland, Grace (Box I-4, Folder 56)
  - Gittens, William (Mrs.) (Box I-4, Folder 57)
  - Hamilton, Lawrence, & Alberto Cruz, Jr. (Box I-4, Folder 58)
    Also business card for Rick Engler of the George Street Playhouse.
  - Hicks, Clarence (Box I-4, Folder 59)
  - High Life, The (Box I-4, Folder 60)
  - Holland, Joe (Box I-4, Folder 61)
    Photographer if identified: Victor Virdi
  - Homeboys in Outer Space (Box I-4, Folder 62)
    Print is attached with a staple to a 2-leaf press release with 1-leaf cover letter from Michael Di Pasquale.
  - Houston, Whitney (Box I-4, Folder 63)
  - Iverem, Esther (Box I-4, Folder 64)
    Photographer if identified: Erica Burger
  - Jackson, Brian (Box I-4, Folder 65)
    Photographer if identified: Lew D. Hamilton
  - Jackson, Freddie (Box I-4, Folder 66)
    Photographer if identified: Carl Studna
  - Jackson, Janet (Box I-4, Folder 67)
    Photographer if identified: Patrick Demarchelier
  - Jackson, Mannie, Culy Neal, & Jesse Jackson (Rev.) (Box I-4, Folder 68)
  - James, Etta (Box I-4, Folder 69)
    Photographer if identified: Anthony Barbosa/Villard Books
  - Jemison, Theodore Judson (Dr.) (Box I-4, Folder 70)
  - Johnson, Doris, Hazel Dulpes, & Morcelle Maxwell (Big Wheels) (Box I-4, Folder 71)
  - Jones, Julie (Box I-4, Folder 72)
  - Jordan, Michael (Box I-4, Folder 73)
  - Jump For Joy (Box I-4, Folder 74)
    Photographer if identified: G. West
  - King, Abuto (Box I-4, Folder 75)
  - Kitt, Eartha (Box I-4, Folder 76)
    Photographer if identified: Raven Chanticleer
  - Kuntukununku, Osagyefo Nana, II (Box I-4, Folder 77)
  - LeMelle, Wilbert J. (Box I-4, Folder 78)
  - Lewis, Cheryl (Box I-4, Folder 79)
  - Mandella, Max (Box I-4, Folder 80)
    Photographer if identified: Boone Photo
  - Miarianax (Lynda Gravatt with cast) (Box I-4, Folder 81)
    Photographer if identified: Rich Pipeling
  - Marino, Dan, & Darius Rucker (Box I-4, Folder 82)
  - McLymont, Fritz-Earle St. Elmo (Box I-4, Folder 83)
    Photographer if identified: Port Authority of NY & NJ
  - Mod Squad (Box I-4, Folder 84)
  - Moore, Gwen (Box I-4, Folder 85)
    Also one halftone print. Photo print has staple through border.
  - Morgan, Dawn (Box I-4, Folder 86)
  - Mumphrey, Kelly (Wedding Bells) (Box I-4, Folder 87)
  - National Baptist Convention (Box I-4, Folder 88)
    Photographer if identified: Sharon D. Keeling
  - New Classic Soul (Box I-4, Folder 89)
  - Nomads of the Wind (Box I-4, Folder 90)
    Photographer if identified: Peter Crawford/BBC
  - Parker, Lori (Box I-4, Folder 91)
  - Pettigrew, Charles, & Eddie Chacon (Box I-4, Folder 92)
  - Pieces of a Dream (Box I-4, Folder 93)
    Photographer if identified: Gene Martin
  - Powell, Mike (Box I-4, Folder 94)
  - Prince, Akili, & Richard Brooks (Box I-4, Folder 95)
    With attached 3-leaf press release for the play Police Boys and computer-printed cover letter signed by Philip Rinalid of Playwright's Horizons dated 4-28-1995.
  - PS 125 (Meeting the Chancellor) (Box I-4, Folder 96)
  - Pudgee (Box I-4, Folder 97)
  - Purvis, Pam, & Bob Ackerman (Box I-4, Folder 98)
  - Quinn, Oliver B. (Box I-4, Folder 99)
  - Richards, Bea (Box I-4, Folder 100)
  - Richardson, Pearl (Box I-4, Folder 101)
  - Robinson, Eddie (Box I-4, Folder 102)
  - Sanders, Kevin (Box I-4, Folder 103)
  - Satcher, David (Dr.) (Box I-4, Folder 104)
  - Service Awards (Box I-4, Folder 105)
  - Sharpton, Al (Rev.) (Box I-4, Folder 106)
  - Silver, Horace (Box I-4, Folder 107)
    Photographer if identified: Caroline Greyshock
  - Simmons, Judy (Box I-4, Folder 108)
  - Sinclair (Box I-4, Folder 109)
  - Sinclair, Abiola, & Benita Porter (Box I-4, Folder 110)
  - Jenkins Brothers, The (Box I-4, Folder 111)
    Also one halftone print. Label on folder: "Singing duo."
  - Smith, Clarence O., & Ellen Cohen (Box I-4, Folder 112)
  - Smith, Joshua (Leadership program) (Box I-4, Folder 113)
  - Solomon-Glover, André (Box I-4, Folder 114)
  - Solomon-Glover, Diana (Box I-4, Folder 115)
  - Stevenson, Joseph (Dr.) (Box I-4, Folder 116)
  - Supporting cast (Box I-4, Folder 117)
    Also one halftone print. Pictured: James Earl Jones & others.
  - Swann, Lynn (For Dancers) (Box I-4, Folder 118)
  - Taylor, Joe (Box I-4, Folder 119)
    Note on folder: "Hampton head football coach."
  - Taylor, M. (Box I-4, Folder 120)
  - Toland, Bernice (Box I-4, Folder 121)
  - Vereen, Ben (Box I-4, Folder 122)
  - Walker Art Center (Box I-4, Folder 123)
  - Whitaker, Forest (Box I-4, Folder 124)
  - Williams, Terrie M. (Box I-4, Folder 125)
  - Wonder women (Box I-4, Folder 126)
    Print has staples through border.
  - Woodruff, Virginia (Box I-4, Folder 127)
  - Dated (Box I-4, Folder 128)
    Also 11 print press releases (19 leaves total), 12 faxed press releases (25 leaves total), photocopy of typed letter signed by Patricia A. Reeberg of the Council of Churches of the City of New York to J. Zamgba Browne dated 4-27-1994 (2 leaves), and faxed text of a commencement speech given by Vernon E. Jordan, Jr. at the North Carolina Central University on 5-14-1994 (13 leaves). 2 prints have staples through border.
  - Dated (Box I-4, Folder 129)
    Also 6 print press releases (18 leaves total) and 15 faxed press releases (28 leaves total).
  - Misc. (Box I-4, Folder 130)
    One bundle of 4 prints attached together with a staple at the corner. 4 additional images have staples through the border. Also one advertising postcard for an event in honor of Toni Cade Bambara, promotional CD Maxwell's Urban Hang Suite, and 9 halftone prints.
    Photographer if identified: Malcolm Pinckney, Allen Morgan, Susan F. Rymshaw, Gloria Gottschalk, NYC Housing Authority Photo Unit, Bill Moore
  - Misc. (Box I-4, Folder 131)
    One print has attached press release (1 leaf). 4 prints have staples through the border. Also 4 halftone prints.
    Photographer if identified: Mount Vernon Ladies' Association, Bill Moore, Gideon Manasseh, Karl Crutchfield, Greg Bell, Gary Gershoff, Allen Morgan, Peterkin Photo
  - [no label] (Box I-4, Folder 132)
    One print is mounted on biographical data sheet, with 5 accompanying leaves of photocopied press clippings.
    Photographer if identified: Michael Levine, Tony Cordoza, Gideon Manasseh, Bill Moore, Julian Broad, Toni Scott, Aldo, Robert Lobe, Don Perdue, Amy Arbus, Lynn Saville, William Abranowicz, Anthology Film Archives, Jimmy Katz/Giant Steps, Lester Cohen, Richard Foreman, Stephanie Berger, NIgel Perry, John Farmer, Chuck Pulin, David Roth, Dennis Williford, Eric Stephen Jacobs, Dagmar Schultz
  - AMNews Pix (Random) (Box I-4, Folder 133)
    Also computer-printed letter from Mabel Richardson to Elinor Tatum (undated), 1 color slide, and 2 leaves removed from an unidentified catalog.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Allen Morgan, G. Balkcom, Frank English, Emily C., James Gilbert
  - [no label] (Box I-4, Folder 134)
    Also one faxed press release with extensive ms. annotations (2 leaves) and one image removed from an unidentified publication. One print has subject bio stapled to verso with staples through corners of image. One image is stapled (through image) to caption, with attached cover letter dated 8-13-1993 from Jennifer Thomas (1 leaf) and 1 leaf of photocopied press clippings. Three prints are attached together with tape at edges. One small print is stuck to the back of a larger print with tape. 3 prints have staples through border.
    Photographer if identified: Klytus, Karl Crutchfield, Martha Swope, William Gibson/Martha Swope Associates, Jonathan Slaff
  - [no label] (Box I-4, Folder 135)
    Also one paste-up for newspaper article "Ivory Coast president dies; Africa's longest reigning ruler" by Peter Da Costa (with one attach halftone print) bio sheet for Di Smith, press release from WLIB-AM (1 leaf), one faxed image, and 3 halftone prints. 2 prints are attached together with tape. 2 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Joseph Sinnott, Joe Pineiro, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Ray Block, Kwame Brathwaite, Gerald Peart, Rick Tango, Allen Morgan
- Series J. Loose Unsorted Items
  Unsorted items found in various locations around the Amsterdam News office.
  - Loose materials from office (Box J-1, Folder 1)
    Also one color photocopy (3 images). Label on inner folder grouped with these prints: "Tatum." Contents of this folder, many of which include ms. notes and corrections: One computer-printed typescript letter signed by Mike Abbott to Bill Tatum dated 8-13-1993, with attached memo concerning building at 350 W 110th St. (2 leaves total); faxed press release from UAW Local 2110 dated 9-14-1993 (1 leaf); faxed editorial letter "For Ebony Williams," undated, by "A Father/The Fathers of All Our Children" (1 leaf); typed letter signed by Bob Brody of the United Way to Bill Tatum dated 9-13-1993, with a story idea on Marble Hill resident Michelle Nelson (2 leaves); computer-printed typescript article text "The Politics of a Tourist Visa" by Bennett Paris (3 leaves); typed letter signed by Masoba A. Dieta to the Amsterdam News dated 8-28-1993 concerning US military action in Somalia (1 leaf); typed letter signed by William R. Frey of the Enterprise Foundation to Cathy Connors/Amsterdam News dated 8-27-1993, concerning Evelyn King's open letter to Mayor Dinkins criticizing the Department of Housing Preservation and Development (1 leaf); faxed "Labor Day Message from Councilmember Una Clarke" dated 8-26-1993 (1 leaf); faxed text "Keeping the Dream Alive" by Stanley Hill dated 8-28-1993 (2 leaves); computer-printed typed letter from Concerned Citizens for Quality Television Programs to "Editor" dated 8-19-1993 concerning discrimination at NBC (2 leaves); computer-printed typescript text "Planned Parenthood Urges Confirmation of Dr. Joycelyn Elders as Surgeon General" by Jacqueline S. Jackson (3 leaves, with photo print stapled to last leaf); computer-printed typescript text "President Clinton to Address Baptists; Mayor Dinkins to Receive Highest Award" by Sylvester Leaks (1 leaf); faxed press release from Patrice Lumumba Coalition dated 8-31-1993 (1 long folded leaf); faxed press release dated 9-7-1993 concerning Lenora Fulani's endorsement of Colin Moore for City Council (1 long folded leaf); faxed letter from Brooklyn borough president Howard Golden to David N. Dinkins dated 8-18-1993, concerning the garbage strike (3 leaves); 3 faxed press releases dated 8-30 and 8-31-1993 concerning the NY Municipal Hospital Worker's Union endorsement of Colin A. Moore (3 leaves total); faxed text, unsigned and undated, concerning police brutality (3 leaves); and a faxed letter with illegible date from Arnie Ruth to Bill Tatum (1 leaf).
  - Loose materials from office (Box J-1, Folder 2)
    Also faxed letter from Jen Bluestein to J. Zamgba Browne dated 7-30-2001, concerning public advocate candidate Betsy Gotbaum (17 leaves total, with attached handbill); faxed press release dated 8-13-2001 concerning Brooklyn borough president candidate Jeannette Gadson (8 leaves); faxed press release dated 8-25-2001 concerning Public Advocate Mark Green's plan to reduce police misconduct (2 leaves); faxed packet of information on the Harriet Tubman Home dated 5-21-2001 (5 leaves); faxed press release dated 8-27-2001 concerning the West Indian Day Parade (4 leaves); faxed press release dated 10-3-2001 concerning Citizens Union's endorsement of Betsy Gotbaum (1 leaf); 2 handbills and one newspaper clipping concerning State Assemblyman Samuel A. Herbert's 2001 reelection campaign; packet of faxed resumes of lawyers (13 leaves); one computer-printed image; program from a memorial service for Dr. Esther Mae Humes Forchalle, held at the Church of God of Prophecy on 12-5-2001; and a brief ms. note dated 8-31-1999 concerning Rev. Titus Walker and E[linor] Tatum (1 leaf).
  - Loose materials from office (Martin Luther King, Duke Ellington) (Box J-1, Folder 3)
    Subjects in folder include Martin Luther King Jr., Fela Kuti, James Baldwin, Charles Kenyatta, Sammy Davis Jr. Also 3 velox prints; a printout of an e-mail from Elinor Tatum to Nayaba Arinde dated 1-2-2009 concerning images of Martin Luther King, Jr. (2 leaves); mailing envelope address to Mel Tapley from E. Horle of RCA/Record Division dated 1-25-1982, containing a 2-leaf press release and a promotional copy of the 7" 45rpm record "Hooked on Ellington" from the musical Duke Ellington's Sophisticated Ladies.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Lorraine Capperell
  - Loose materials from office (book manuscripts) (Box J-1, Folder 4)
    Photocopied manuscripts of two books: David Dinkins and the Goliaths of New York City: The 1989 Mayoral Campaign by Basil Wilson (76 leaves) and Black-on-Black Homicides: Crisis in Bridgeport, Connecticut by Craig Kelly (22 leaves, dated Sept. 1990).
  - Loose materials from office (photos) (Box J-1, Folder 5)
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Allen Morgan, Roxanne Butters, Milton Grant/United Nations
  - Loose materials from office (Civil Rights marches - photos) (Box J-1, Folder 6)
    14 of the prints in this group are grouped together in an inner folder labeled "Civil Rights Marches, Etc."; 4 prints are grouped in an unlabeled inner folder.
    Photographer if identified: Jeff Connell, Nichols, Bill Carter, Sam Reiss, Friedman-Abeles, Bill Moore, James Gilbert, James C. Campbell
  - Loose materials from office (Job applications) (Box J-1, Folder 7)
    30 "Application for Employment" forms for the Amsterdam News from 1966-1969. 4 have attached resumes (8 leaves total). 3 have attached typed cover letters signed by Edna L. Spencer to Jesse Walker, dated 9-26-1969, 7-17, 1969, and 4-9-1969. One has attached autograph letter signed by Jefferson D. Diggs III (1 leaf) and manuscript "Employment Summary" by Jefferson D. Diggs III (2 leaves). One has attached ms. note (unsigned and undated, 1 leaf). One has attached typed cover letter signed by Leonard Anthony Casso dated 5-13-1966 and attached ms. note from "Jan" to "Millie." One has attached photocopy of a reference letter signed by Joe King. Also one ms. phone message note, dated 3/10/[no year]; typed letter signed by Albina Sprague to Jesse Walker dated 2-10-1969, concerning the sale of a home (1 leaf), typed letter signed by John P. Fennell to Jesse Walker dated 2-11-1969 (1 leaf); typed letter signed by Cellestine Ware to Jesse Walker dated 2-18-1969 (1 leaf, with attached 1-leaf resume); typed letter signed by Henry Mara (undated, 1 leaf), with attached resume (2 leaves) and original mailing envelope; typed letter signed by Carol Len Park to Jesse Walker dated 2-19-1969 (2 leaves) and original mailing envelope; typed letter signed by Ron Howard (Sager) to Jesse Walker dated 2-17-1969 (1 leaf); typed memo from Dianne Thompson to Jesse Walker (1 leaf, with attached 2-leaf resume); typed letter signed by Miguel E. Graham dated 6-2-1969 (1 leaf); typed letter signed by Madeline Weisberger to Jesse Walker dated 2-11-1969 (1 leaf); and typed letter signed by "Doc" Young to Jesse Walker dated 2-22-1969 (1 leaf).
  - Loose material (Amsterdam News History) (Box J-1, Folder 8)
    Also flier for Dorothea Towles Church Salon (7-26-2008); ms. note concerning an unnamed event on 1-19-1999; and an inner folder labeled "Amsterdam News History" containing: the Excelsior Empire Savings Bank News vol. 1, no. 2 (Jan. 1968) (4 copies); photocopied text "History of the New York Amsterdam News" by James Booker (3 copies, each 2 leaves); newspaper clipping attached to an unsigned ms. note; typescript text "Amst. News history" by Hicks (3 leaves); ms. note dated 2-8-1960; photocopied Statement of Ownership dated 10-1-1963 (1 leaf); flier for the Amsterdam News ca. 1961 (2 copies); offprint article "Image Building Necessary in the Negro National Community" by D. Parke Gibson, reprinted from the Oct. 1965 issue of Public Relations Journal (1 leaf); and one photo print (included in print count).
  - Loose material (Entertainment press photos) (Box J-1, Folder 9)
    Also 4-leaf bio of Ron Scott. One print has attached bio of Rose Jackson (3 leaf).
    Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan Photo Service, Walter H. Scott, Frank Stewart, Jacki Sallow, Shelia Turner, Trilobite
  - Loose material (Entertainment press photos) (Box J-1, Folder 10)
    Also press materials for the television show New York Undercover (4 leaves total); bio of Richie Havens (3 leaves); bio of Clark Johnson (3 leaves); printed envelope accompanying photos from the film Virtuosity.
    Photographer if identified: Jean Weisinger, Mel Wright, Marc Joseph, Sidney Baldwin, Bruce Birmelin
  - Loose material (Entertainment press photos) (Box J-1, Folder 11)
    Also 7 press releases (19 leaves total); computer-printed typescript text "Dance Theatre of Harlem: A Review" by Deirdre Donovan (3 leaves); and manuscript text on Black Books Plus (3 leaves).
    Photographer if identified: Marc Joseph, Adam Friedman, Thierry Leqoues, Lisa Peardon, Humphrey Studio, Misha Kogan, Lloyd Wright
  - Loose material (Entertainment press photos) (Box J-1, Folder 12)
    Also two computer-printed images (with attached ms. note dated 6-30-1995).
  - Loose material (Entertainment press photos) (Box J-1, Folder 13)
    Also autograph letter signed by Kevin Maynor to Mel [Tapley] (1 leaf), one-leaf bio of Mary Bentley-LaMar, ms. note from Ron Scott to Mel [Tapley] dated 10-27-[no year] (1 leaf), and printed envelope containing photos from the film Independence Day.
    Photographer if identified: Julie Lemberger, Annie Leahy, Susan Biddle, Sky Bergman, Thomas Dallal, Trudy Dittmar, Joanne Savio, Phil Parmet, Allan Barker,, Sarah Perry, Cy White, Lorey Sebastian, Christian Steiner, Kenneth Mills, Claudette Barius, Stephen Vaughan, Gloria Baker, Mike Jones, Francesco Scavullo, Gerald Henry, Coreen Simpson
  - Loose material (Entertainment press photos) (Box J-1, Folder 14)
    Also 3 press releases (8 leaves total).
    Photographer if identified: Randee St. Nicholas, Andrew Eccles, Chris Bennion, Howard Gordon, Deborah Boardman, Rolf Konow, Audrian, Karl Crutchfield
  - Loose material (Entertainment press photos) (Box J-1, Folder 15)
    Also pamphlet Master Lover's Sex Pamphlet by Freddie L. Sirmans and one velox print. One print has attached packet of photocopied press clippings (5 leaves).
  - Loose material (Jeff Diggs) [empty folder] (Box J-1, Folder 16)
  - Loose material (Entertainment press photos) (Box J-1, Folder 17)